[
  {
    "front": "usage, emploi, chose à faire, user, employer",
    "back": "用"
  },
  {
    "front": "maladie, malade",
    "back": "病"
  },
  {
    "front": "institution",
    "back": "院"
  },
  {
    "front": "réfléchir, refléter",
    "back": "映"
  },
  {
    "front": "image",
    "back": "画"
  },
  {
    "front": "socle, support, plateau, (suffixe) machine",
    "back": "台"
  },
  {
    "front": "mourir",
    "back": "死"
  },
  {
    "front": "qualité, nature",
    "back": "質"
  },
  {
    "front": "question, problème",
    "back": "問"
  },
  {
    "front": "thème, sujet",
    "back": "題"
  }
]
